What's wrong?
What?
Why are you
so quiet?
No reason.
You nervous?
Hell no.
I'm just thinking...
What if, uh...
...this Huffman fucker
shows up traveling light?
I don't know...
How light?
I don't know,
let's say half.
Half, I think
that buys him
about a day.
Nothing more than that,
but we're not blackmailing
this guy in installments.
What if he shows up
with 50 or 60 grand?
That's just
an insult.
Anything less
than 100,000,
so this guy knows
we mean business.
Did you bring
the bleach?
'Cause I didn't.
There's nothing
to worry about,
this guy's scared.
He wouldn't dare
try and stiff us.
Yeah, he wouldn't
'cause we're no
dumb-ass custodians.
Oh, shit,
there he is.
With a bag.
We're on.
Uh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh.
I, uh, came alone
like you said.
Smart man.
Let's see
the green.
Oh.
And my DVDs?
Right here,
Fellini.
Toss us the bag,
and you can take your
dirty movies and go.
-  As a kid I used to think
-  I was gonna be somebody,
a model citizen raising
a family in the suburbs.
Being shot at by a psycho
with a machine gun
was not part of the plan.
Now, all I can think
to myself is...
...how the fuck
did I get here?
¶ Hey
¶
¶ She stole my breath,
one of the best
¶ And like the rest,
I think I need an exorcist
¶ Well, I'm a mess, baby,
I'm possessed maybe
¶ I've got a heartache,
man, to fix
¶ Call a doctor,
call a preacher
¶ Please, I'm a wreck, please,
you see I gotta meet her
¶ Somebody sitting here,
somebody said hey
¶ Somebody sitting there,
ah
¶
Right. Is it always too
complicated for you?
Cosmo is $6.00.
How about, uh...
How about an  Us Weekly?
No, Cosmo  has four times
the amount of pages.
Guns & Ammo
looks pretty sturdy too.
Listen to me.
Cosmo  is the sturdiest.
¶
¶ You hold the sun ¶
Park your butt here, honey.
Yeah?
Give me your arm.
Your other arm...
I don't wanna wipe
your ass for you.
You're never gonna
know what my shoe
says about me.
The cast was
a great idea.
It's definitely
gonna look like
you broke your arm.
You know, this isn't
gonna fool 'em.
Your brother's
not that stupid.
He's not gonna
look that closely.
But, you know,
I can always
make it for real.
You'd like that,
wouldn't you?
Mmm-hmm, some days
more than others.
Rarely ever question
the things you do for love.
I just wanted a family.
Beverly, well,
she always wanted more.
out of a bank robbery
that her own brother planned.
Man, this woman's got
a hold on me.
¶
Make sure you
get out of the job
no matter what.
Make him talk you
out of it.
I know.
It was only
a little accident,
nothing major...
I... I know.
Okay.
Because if he suspects
anything, baby...
Do you wanna
talk to him for me?
I wish that I could.
Mmm.
Please don't
fuck this up.
I love you.
Love you.
No real names, okay?
You're Steve,
you're fucking Carl.
All right?
All right.
Remember, at the fucking
scene, you call me Gary.
What the fuck?
Before you start,
before you say anything,
I just wanna say
it was a small accident.
I had one drink,
fell asleep at the wheel.
Car's fucked,
arm's fucked...
I'm fine, though.
I'm totally gonna
be able to do this job
one-handed, all good.
Our wheel man gets
in a car accident?
Fucking awesome.
Seriously, who...
How did he get
this job, huh?
Did you fuck him?
Tell.
You know what my father
used to tell me?
"Trust in the Lord
with all your heart,
"and lean not on your
own understanding."
It means God has
a plan for you, son,
no matter
how stupid you are.
Hmm.
But now, somehow,
we're all being punished
for bringing you on.
Now, I gotta rethink
the whole fucking
plan, dickhead!
Right here, right now,
this is what
we're fucking doing.
We need to get
to the bank
at 5:00 p.m.,
right before
it closes, okay?
The plan worked
just like I told you.
Hold it.
Anything?
Not even a scratch.
Shit.
I have an idea.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
no, no, no, no, no.
No, not gonna use
a sledgehammer, don't...
We have been here
for, like, an hour.
Well, find something else.
It's gonna work,
just shut up.
Jesus, do you
love me or not?
One...
That's such
a bad idea.
Two...
Oh, fuck.
¶
Let's go, let's go!
Yes, I need to report
a bank robbery in progress.
It's on the corner
of 12th and Main.
Please hurry,
I think I heard gunshots!
We have a possible
211 in progress
at the Bank of America.
We have shots fired.
Shit.
This is the LAPD.
Put down your weapons,
come out with your hands up.
Go, go, go, go!
Beverly?
It went fucking
perfect, perfect.
Just like you said.
Okay, that's perfect.
Did anyone
follow you?
No, no,
they all got shot.
Everybody got shot.
They shot Ray first.
I don't know if he's dead,
I don't know if he's alive.
Baby, there's a million
fucking dollars in there.
Oh...
Can we just
fucking go?
You gotta take me
to a hospital, okay?
My arm is fucking
killing me...
Baby, we just stole
a million dollars.
Your arm is the least
of our problems, okay?
This is amazing.
We should go,
we should go.
Oh, fuck.
Are you fucking
kidding me?
Oh, no.
Oh, fuck.
I ask you to
do one thing,
one fucking thing...
Don't let anyone
follow you back.
Sorry, I... Shit.
I can't go to prison.
I can't go to prison...
I can't...
Bev...
Oh!
Oh... Oh.
I...
I can't go to prison.
Why did you...
Why did you do
that, Beverly?
I'm sorry.
Oh!
Don't be mad!
You know, I was hoping
for some kind of
cool white
flash-before-my-eyes montage
or a reassuring light
at the end of the tunnel.
Instead, I found
the TV remote.
I don't know if it was
because my wife betrayed me
or because I was about to lose
a million dollars,
but whatever it was,
something came over me.
¶
Hey, buddy.
Hey, buddy?
Holy shit.
Jesus Christ.
LA Police Department,
how can I help you?
Hey, hey, hey,
there's a guy,
he's on the street.
He's bleeding...
I think he's dead.
Fuck, I think he's dead.
May the Lord
in His kindness,
and His wisdom,
and His generosity,
and His love,
and His caring,
and His full heart
accept you into Heaven
as you leave this earth.
- What are you...
- What are you doing?
This is Father Matthews,
he's giving you
your last rites.
I'm dying?
I'm afraid so.
You suffered a gunshot
wound to the spleen,
causing internal
bleeding and severe
renal failure.
I called a priest in
because you only have
a few minutes to live.
Before you
can enter heaven,
before you
receive the sacrament
of penance,
you must unburden
yourself of sin.
You must tell
God where you
hid the money.
Otherwise, how
can you ascend?
I'm dying?
It's a cute act,
but I get it.
You boys are the heat.
Detective Ashton.
This is
Detective Morton,
my partner.
The  Playhouse 90 routine,
that was my idea.
Detective Ashton
here just wanted
to kick your ass
until you talked.
Talk about what?
Your buddy...
He made a deal
and gave you up.
So we have
you for receiving
stolen goods.
You're going
away for three
years for that.
However, today
is your lucky day
'cause if you tell us
where the money is,
you walk
out of here
free and clear.
Well, 'cause that...
That sounds like
an official,
city-backed offer.
I'm sorry, boys.
Money burned up
in the fire.
Come on...
A loser like you?
You'd burn alive
before you left
that money behind.
Look.
We know that you
went to the Jefferson
Hotel, all right?
We know that you used
your master key
to get into
one of the rooms.
And we know that
you stole some clothes
from a Japanese
tourist...
Remember this?
You made a huge
fucking mess.
Look, we know that's
where you hid the money,
and when we find it,
it's 10 to 15 years.
Do yourself
a favor.
Give us the money,
all right?
A face like
that in prison?
You're gonna
be eating dick
by lunchtime.
Dick that's
been in your ass.
Money burned up
in the fire.
All right, fuck it,
we do it my way.
Morton, start
writing on his chart.
Besides the gunshot
wound and
the broken arm,
he suffers from
severe hematomas and
a shattered kneecap.
Hematomas...
How do you spell
"hematomas"?
H-E...
I'm just gonna
put "bruising."
You're not gonna torture me,
you guys are cops.
We don't use that word.
That's an ugly word.
Yes, ugly.
I just need to make
sure you don't know
where the money is.
Oh, come on.
Hey, hey, hey, I...
Oh!
¶
Hmm.
Ethan Tell.
I'll be your
parole officer for
the next 18 months
unless, of course,
you do something stupid
and find yourself
back in here.
Not a good move.
Here are your
parole instructions.
In a nutshell,
don't leave LA.
Don't hang out
with any felons,
any convicts,
or anyone who has
access to a firearm.
Say that you just
found God on your...
Your release
and your pastor
wants to invite you
over for dinner
to meet his gorgeous
virgin daughter,
who has big titties
and big nipples.
Well, say you're at dinner,
and there's a Civil War rifle
that hasn't been shot
in a hundred years,
right over dinner,
right over the potato salad.
I suggest you get
the fuck out of there
and stay away from
that man, his church,
his daughter,
and her big nipples
because they're trying
to throw you back in jail.
That's a violation.
Here's your keys
to the halfway house.
It's a residential facility,
not a jail cell,
so there's no fucking
in the shower,
there's no peeing
in the sink.
All the stuff
you do in here? Mmm-mmm.
It's a nice place,
keep it clean.
Are we clear?
Yeah.
I'll see you every Tuesday,
10:30 sharp,
no exceptions,
no excuses.
No bullshit.
See? I like you.
Pick a candy...
Not the purple ones,
I love those.
And don't do
anything stupid.
All right, they wanna
know where you stash
your cash at.
Don't try to skip town,
make a run for it.
You won't
get half a block
with every cop
in the city...
...watching you.
So if I were you,
play it cool,
and tomorrow...
I'll help you.
Help me what?
Get the cash.
Mr. Johnson, uh,
the cash burned
up in the fire.
I like that,
keep it like that.
Convict on deck!
Parolee.
Yeah.
Tell?
Tell!
I'm unarmed.
You look good.
Sorry I never came
to visit you in prison.
I wrote to
you, though.
Yeah.
Divorce letter?
I... I got that one.
That was just so
they wouldn't think
I was an accomplice.
Smart.
You know, I, uh...
I wrote you letters.
I was kind of hoping
that when you got out,
some time would
pass, and then
maybe you'd be able
to forgive me?
For what,
shooting me
or not visiting
me in prison?
Both, actually.
Can I give
you a ride?
We can talk,
catch up maybe.
It's good
seeing you, Bev.
It was always
just you and me.
Just one cup
of coffee, please.
You know, it's gonna
take more than a couple
of donuts, Bev.
When I shot you,
I was off my ass.
Like, clean off my ass.
What does
that mean?
All those promises
you made,
how you were gonna
take care of me,
I believed them,
every single
one of them because
I loved you.
And all of that
drove me...
Just clean
off your ass.
And then, the police
showed up,
and I panicked.
But everything's
different now.
I mean,
I have changed,
and you're rich.
Excuse me?
What?
Oh, your bank money.
Ours,
if you still love me,
which I don't...
Money burned up
at the house, Bev,
it's not there.
Money's gone.
Do you still love me?
Hmm?
Of course
I still love you.
Hmm.
If there's no money,
then there's
no money, babe.
We have each other.
I love you.
Is there really
no money?
Sorry.
So this morning,
when I was
getting ready,
I realized that
you and I haven't
seen each other
for three years.
So I only
wore this.
But I mean,
you probably don't
want me, do you?
Mm.
How do you like
them donuts, huh?
I lied to you earlier
about being armed.
That surprises me.
Relax.
It's for you.
What the hell
am I supposed
to do with this?
Ray's getting
out of prison
this week.
No, Ray got
7 to 10.
No, they're
letting him out
on good behavior.
You know
why, right?
The police are
gonna let him out
just to see
if he can lead them
to the money.
Ray's gonna kill you,
So you're giving
me a gun to kill
your brother?
No, to protect
yourself.
Jesus.
I'm just gonna
get dressed.
I wanna
show you something.
What's this place?
See that house?
That's where I live.
When I shot you,
I didn't know
at the time, Tell,
that I was
carrying your child.
Wait, what?
I wanted to
tell you, I did.
That's why I wrote
all those letters.
I wanted to tell you,
I just... Couldn't.
Please don't hate me.
Bev, we have a kid?
He's a beautiful boy.
Oh.
I couldn't raise
him by myself
I mean, I was alone,
I was pregnant,
I was broke.
The only reason
I divorced you
was because
I needed to marry
another man so
he could support me.
Wait, what?
You're married?
I met Arthur
through my cousin.
He's quite amazing,
actually.
He takes really
good care of us.
You're married, you live
in that house with some guy
and my kid, and
he calls him "Daddy"?
Only while you were
in prison.
Now that you're out
and you have the money,
I will divorce him
and marry you,
and we can be together,
and be a family, and...
You're off your ass.
Where are you going?
To get my son
away from you
and your crazy.
No, no, no,
you can't do that.
Just give me the gun,
you have to
get out of here.
Let me go.
Just come with me,
just come...
I'm not leaving
without my kid.
Shit.
What did
you do?
Okay, you have
to get out of here.
Just go, just go,
just go.
Do you wanna
go back to prison?
Wait! Tell!
Really?
You need that.
Good morning,
gentlemen.
Anyone interested
in an honest
day's pay?
Tax free.
Next time.
Here we are,
home sweet home.
Father Frank and I live
in the parish house,
and we rented out
the apartment
to the church
custodian for the last
couple of years.
But now, it needs
to be emptied out.
Oh, he's not
living here anymore?
No, he...
It was a suicide.
Nice.
So you want
this whole place
cleaned up?
Yes, indeed, clean,
clean, clean.
The man
committed suicide.
That's a sin in
the eyes of the church
and the Lord.
So everything has
to go, everything.
We can't keep it,
we can't donate it.
Everything's gotta go.
Look, it's not
a dream job.
It's more of a nightmare.
But... Look it here,
the keys!
To the pickup, you said
how cool it was, so...
...you can haul
everything away on that...
And, uh, this could
be the beginning
of you turning
your life around.
¶
Hi.
Shit.
Jesus Christ,
you don't show up
at somebody's house.
Bev, I brought
this for him.
So what?
What the hell is
wrong with you?
Come on.
God, what would you
have done if my husband
answered the door?
I don't know,
"Hi, I'm Tell,
I'm her other husband."
You stupid idiot...
Get in the car, drive!
Go! Get in the car!
Shh.
Hurry!
Okay, if I had a son,
I wanna see him.
Well, you can't
see him.
You told me
you loved me.
Jesus, Tell,
that was before
I knew you were broke.
I am not gonna
leave my husband
if you don't
have the money.
Wait a minute.
So you're gonna
dangle our son as bait
because you think
I'm lying about
having "the money."
And you're here
just to make sure
he looks like you.
Am I right?
Okay, I'm gonna
be honest with you.
No shit.
I had the money when
I got out of the house.
But when I was
looking for
a place to stash it,
I passed out
on the street
from blood loss
because someone
shot me.
Then, when I woke up
in the hospital...
Money was gone.
Hmm.
Your turn.
Okay, okay.
His name is William,
after your father
because is he your son.
And yes, I love you,
and I want us
to be a family.
I really do.
But if you can't
support William,
then I have to be
with someone who can.
It's just
smart parenting.
Please don't
come back here,
for William's sake.
Oh, this was
very thoughtful.
Oh...
¶ It's spun out of control
¶
¶ Let me tell you about
the life I live
¶ Fuck you
and your icy wrists
¶ Out of game, man,
life's a bitch
¶ Singing nights like this,
I wish
¶ Days I suffer so
when I puff the droll
¶ And if you got to know, then
I'm a motherfuckin' outlaw
¶ Southpaw switch it up
for your ditty, though
¶ Nigga got a uppercut,
he ain't getting up
¶ You don't love me, bitch,
don't lie to me
¶ Guys like me die violently
¶ In the street with my heat
on the side of me
¶ I wonder why fights
are quite obsolete
¶ I'm gonna need four-five
for me, obviously
¶ I, I am still in the mirror
¶ Like good, god damn,
something gotta shake
¶ Let him live,
that's my mistake
¶ I want the bread, the cake,
I want the cheese, the fruit
¶ I want all food groups
and a coupe for two
¶ Come through
like I usually do
¶ Super smooth, and nigga,
you will move ¶
¶
¶ There's something
to be said
¶ Of being
a man of few words
¶ 'Cause I fade
the final four lines
¶ Nothing is
an empty nest
¶ Well, I found out... ¶
You know what?
I think
that you boys need
to take a refresher
on surveillance.
We figured there
was no harm
coming in here,
It's cold outside...
Don't worry,
relax, relax.
All right,
we're not here to
cause any trouble.
We don't even care
about the rod
Or the fact that
you used it to shoot up
a neighborhood.
Or that you
were giving it
to your ex-wife
in a public
parking lot.
That's against
the law, by the way.
What do you say
to a friendly drink?
Hey, can we
get two shots
of whiskey,
and whatever
my friend
is having?
Look, guys,
just like I said
three years ago,
the money...
Burned up in the fire,
so excuse me.
Get up, get up.
Get up, get up,
get up.
God.
There you go.
Do not bleed on me.
There you go,
there you go.
You know
what I think?
I think we got off
to a bad start.
Shh, shh,
shh, shh, shh.
Don't give me
some lame-ass excuse.
I don't even think
you have the money.
But Morton here,
he's unsure.
So we're gonna
stick around just
to make sure.
So why don't you,
uh, just skip the part
where you mouth off
and just politely
deal with our
harassment, okay?
Hmm.
Look how much
nicer he looks with
his mouth shut, huh?
I'm so glad
I got that off
of my chest.
I feel better already.
I'm so proud
of you.
Cheers to
old acquaintances
reunited.
And making amends.
Hit us.
Well...
Where... Where am I?
Your room
at the halfway house,
on the floor.
Those detectives
dropped you off
about an hour ago.
Those guys just
beat you enough
to put you
out of commission
for the night,
so we gotta talk now.
They should have
dropped me in the bed.
I got something
for that, cowboy, come on.
Okay, okay.
You know,
they're gonna come back
night after night
until you give in,
or your ex-partner's
gonna kill you.
Let me guess...
You're gonna give me...
...look behind
door number three.
We go with my plan...
It's simple and easy.
You tell me where
the money is,
I go get it,
we split it,  arrivederci.
Look, I passed out
in the middle
of the street
from blood loss,
and when I woke up
in the hospital,
the money was gone.
So it didn't burn up
in this fucking
miraculous fire you
keep telling me about?
See? I knew
your ass was lying.
When you came in
with that fire bullshit,
I was, like,
"This motherfucker lying."
But now we on the same team,
it's... We're building trust.
We'll talk about it
at your weekly.
But until then,
I need you to stay low.
Yeah.
And look, I'm gonna
leave a little edge
under your pillow.
A little edge
under the pillow.
Okay.
¶
Soccer.
Eurotrash.
Hi.
Ray?
Where's my money, Tell?
Oh, you can just
cut me out of here,
and we can talk.
Ah.
Where's my money?
Um, I don't have it.
Okay?
I don't have it.
Someone stole it
when I passed out
on the street.
I'm sorry,
it's gone.
Uh... Ray.
Where... Where is it...
Where... Where is it,
though, seriously?
Don't...
Don't do this, okay?
The money's gone.
Yeah.
You're fucking
lying, Tell.
You... You don't
have the money, okay?
Oh!
Fuck you!
Damn it, okay...
You fucking liar!
You fucking left me
to die there!
That was our fucking plan!
It doesn't matter...
And you left me
to fucking die there!
I found the safe.
You... You found the safe?
Yes, you can take it,
it's all yours.
You want me to do
fucking back flips?
Tell, I'm gonna
fucking plunge this thing.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm gonna
fucking plunge it.
Ray, do not
plunge that, Ray!
Okay, okay?
Bye-bye, Tell.
Please don't
plunge it, Ray.
Ray, Ray!
Fuck you!
Oh, God!
Why? I told you
the truth, okay.
Why would you
do this, all right?
I passed out!
You've got
10 seconds to live...
Where's my goddamn money?
I told you I don't
have the money!
I passed out on the
street, it was gone!
Fuck!
Damn it,
Ray, you just...
...you just killed me
for no reason.
Why'd you do that?
Fuck me!
You really did
lose the fucking
money, didn't you?
Oh, yeah.
Oh, you son of a bitch!
Oh, I really
thought there was
bleach in there.
Ah, that's
just water.
So where's
this fucking safe?
One time on
The Untouchables,
Robert Stack shot
a wall safe open.
You think
that would work?
Do I look like
I even have a gun?
Just saying... What if?
I've been
out of prison for
a fucking day.
Where would
I get a gun?
I don't know.
I've been out
for three days,
don't look at me.
It would probably
just bend the fucking
metal anyway.
Unless you blew
the lock clean off.
That'd be pretty
fucking cool.
Ah, what the hell,
it's worth a shot.
Ray... I knew
you would...
Turn the TV volume
all the way up.
Shit.
Ray.
You can't shoot...
Shit!
I didn't blow it
clean off.
You told me you
didn't have a gun.
How the fuck
am I gonna get
into it now?
You said... Why...
Where did you
get the gun from?
Ah, fuck.
Ray, the gun...
Where did you
get the gun?
Fucking Bev
gave it to me.
Oh.
She gave you that.
Yeah.
Aw, bitch.
There better be
something good in
here, Tell, seriously.
Ray, it's a safe.
You keep money,
jewels, important
stuff in safes!
Ah! Ha, ha!
Shit, that worked.
It's just a bunch
of fucking
tax papers, man.
What the fuck
is this shit?
What is that?
Uh-buh-buh-buh-buh-bah.
I was asking myself.
I'm keeping
this shit.
Okay.
Yeah, it's mine.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, one...
One more thing.
This is for
the bank shit.
Oh!
Shit.
Jesus, Tell,
every time
I see you,
you're bleeding
from someplace new.
What happened?
Well...
I ran into
an old friend.
And then, I ran
into a shovel.
And, um...
You know,
just a normal
day at the office.
Ray?
What are you doing here?
I know I told you
that we shouldn't
see each
other anymore,
but I wanted
to give you this.
What's this?
It's a photo
of our son, William.
It was taken
this Halloween.
Help me understand
something, Bev.
I'm not allowed
to see this kid.
Why is it so important
for you to prove to me
that I'm his father?
Because...
I want you to know
that I am telling
you the truth.
I don't want you
to think I would use
something like this
to get the money.
I want you
to believe me.
I want you to believe
in me, I guess.
That needs to be
cleaned better.
Sit on the bed.
Oh, hey, guess what
Ray showed me today.
A giant-ass hand
cannon you gave him.
He came to see me...
Ow!
Right after prison...
What was I supposed to do?
Hey, Bev, how many
guys have you given
guns to this week?
What did you
want me to say?
"I'm sorry, Ray,
I can't give you a gun
"because I've already
given Tell one
You give him a .44
and you give me, what,
this little pea shooter?
Come on, Tell,
you've always been
a better shot than him.
That's beside
the point.
Beverly, don't
think I'm stupid.
You're trying
to play me against
your brother
in hopes that
whoever is left
standing in the end
shares the money
with you.
Am I right?
and I'm not
gonna fucking
clean it up.
I love you.
It's good
seeing you.
You too!
Fellas, it's about time
you got here to help.
I tell you what...
Why don't you guys
take the dresser?
I'll carry up the pillows.
I'm calling a time-out.
Yeah, okay.
We're hungry,
and we wanna get
something to eat.
If you don't
mind me saying,
that bitch is your
fucking kryptonite.
Why don't you
stay away from her?
You know,
I would if I could.
Uh, we think
you're gonna be
picking up the money
at a steak place
over on Melrose,
so we're gonna
sit there,
surveil you...
Okay, so you're gonna get
a free steak out of me.
And a couple
bottles of wine.
Sure.
Put your hands
under the table.
I don't wanna see
your handcuffs.
All right, good,
give me hunger.
Now put your head down
like you're
a little depressed,
but not that depressed.
There you go.
Ooh, yes, that's it,
make me feel it.
Come on, sit down.
Gentlemen,
is everything okay?
Can I get you
anything else?
Can I have
more wine?
Mmm-hmm, yeah.
Sorry, we can't
order you
anything to eat.
Three entrees
on the check would
stand out in accounting.
Plus, it'd
be dishonest.
Hmm.
Have a roll.
You know,
I figure since...
I mean, we're pals
now, right, guys?
You know,
what if I told you
what really happened
to the bank money?
Yeah.
I'll tell you.
I had it when I got
out of the house.
...then, I passed out
on the street,
and someone
stole it from me.
So if you guys
find that person,
would you tell me?
Because I really
want that money back.
It's mine.
Yuk it up while
you can, smart guy.
Fuck, I already had
"Yuk it up with idiot
detectives" on my calendar.
Boom, I win.
You did win.
He's good.
You're here early.
Uh-huh.
Let's talk
somewhere else, okay?
Step into my office.
Did you think
about what we talked
about last night?
I'm just here
for my weekly.
Forget about that.
I think
you're getting hung up
on the word "officer"
in my job title.
I'm not a law man...
I'm a working stiff.
So if you tell me
where the money is,
I'm not gonna turn
it over to the police.
What's this?
It's my criminal record.
I lifted it from the file.
Whoa.
Listen, nothing too heavy.
I'm not a peeping Tom,
but kind of like
a peeping Tom.
I was trying to steal a TV,
but she just
happened to be naked.
Just stuff like that.
The money's gone...
So here, I...
No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
Just read it, okay?
Just read it.
I've already
committed a felony
by letting you have it.
It's already a crime.
We're doing
crime right now.
So we might as well
go ahead and
jump out the window.
Yeah.
Okay?
Look, there's no "I"
in "crime," man.
Is there an "I" in crime?
You really don't
have that money.
No.
Hey, man,
I... I'm really sorry
about yesterday,
you know,
the shovel, and the
bleach, and all that.
Can we just
call it even?
because I fucking
found something
in that safe. Get in.
Wait, Ray, Ray.
Where are we going?
My place
to talk business.
Listen, there's
a couple of cops...
Oh, your...
Your friends won't
be joining us.
I put a banana
in the tailpipe.
I saw it
in a movie once.
Oh, I'm staying
in the back,
it's fucking awesome.
Beverly's letting
you stay here?
Yeah, dude,
just for
a few months.
I don't know
if you'd call it
a guest house,
or a cabana maybe,
or a detached
garage unit,
or a small,
independent
dwelling,
but it sure beats
the shit out of
your halfway hole.
This time of day,
nobody's home.
Oh, fuck yeah,
chicken.
So, uh, the guy
that lives here,
he an asshole?
Totally.
So this dead guy
you've been
cleaning up after,
he didn't
kill himself.
He was taken out.
Somebody stopped
the dude's clock
and made it
look like a suicide.
Why would
someone do that?
He wasn't just
a church custodian.
at the
Reynolds headquarters
in Santa Monica.
So check this out.
He's up there
every night
sweeping up,
and poking around
in people's desks
for spare change,
credit cards,
whatever he could
fucking find
worth lifting.
Yeah, but you don't
kill a guy for that.
No, you don't.
But one night,
Mr. Paul finds himself
in the office of fucking
Vice President of Sales
Graham Huffman.
He's doing
a little poking around,
and he finds these babies.
Bam!
This, my friend,
is amateur porn
starring Huffman
and about 27
fucking prostitutes.
Shot right in his office.
He's doing
'em on his desk.
He's doing 'em
on his fucking couch.
The orange one,
my favorite.
He's fucking
three of 'em
standing at the window
overlooking downtown.
You've got
'em memorized.
Of course I do.
So Mr. Paul figures
he hit the blackmail
fucking jackpot,
swipes the DVDs,
sends Huffman
a little letter
demanding 200 grand
to get 'em back
or Huffman's wife and kids
get a private screening.
Instead of
paying the guy,
Huffman kills him.
Makes it look
like suicide.
Son of a bitch.
Mmm-hmm.
You wanna pick
up where Mr. Paul
left off, don't you?
Mmm-hmm, but we're
gonna be more careful
because it's two guys
blackmailing him,
and so he's not gonna
try anything cute.
That's why
you apologized,
shit.
Good plan, right?
Okay, I'm in.
Hey, do you wanna
watch the orange one...
With me?
Hey, so when we go see
this Huffman guy,
we gotta look
like we're successful,
like we don't even
need his money,
like we're just
blackmailing him for fun.
Whoa.
How do I look?
You look like
Don fucking Johnson.
That's exactly right.
Get out of
my fucking way!
Not bad.
Hey.
Huffman,
how are you?
Listen, uh,
we're gonna need
that money.
Now.
And if you don't
present it...
Now.
Really bad things
are gonna happen.
Now.
You mess with the bull,
you get the horns.
Hey, where do you
think the guy keeps
the hair gel around here?
Definitely look
like 200,000 now.
Change of
plans, buddy.
We're blackmailing
that son of a bitch
for the return of
his dirty movies and
Mr. Paul's murder.
Together, that's more,
like, 500 grand.
So what happens
if he comes up short?
He's a
Senior Vice President
in charge of sales, man.
If he doesn't have it,
he can embezzle it.
And guess what?
If he does that,
we'll go back
and we'll blackmail
him for that too.
It's the circle
of life, man.
Hakuna matata, bitch!
Hey, I don't
have to, uh...
I don't have to tell
you not to tell Bev
about any of this, do I?
Right.
This is
between us, okay?
This is our business.
So me and Ray
are blackmailing
this executive
from Reynolds Metals.
He's pretty
high up.
We've got some
good stuff on him.
You and Ray?
Yeah.
If only you weren't
interested in a man
who wants to kill you.
He doesn't wanna
kill me, okay?
I got it.
We're gonna take
this guy for 500k,
and then,
after tomorrow,
I will be able to
support you and William.
We'll be a family.
We'll start over.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
Offer still open?
Of course it is.
You know that it is.
I remember my first time.
Ricky Watson.
He was my best friend
in the third grade.
He was my only friend
He had this
Spider-Man comic book.
Wouldn't let
anybody else read it.
I had to have it.
He was bigger than me,
so I found some shit on him,
blackmailed the fuck
out of him.
He wasn't
my friend anymore,
but at least
I got the comic book.
That's nothing, dude.
My first time blackmailing
was my own dad.
My old man was always
running around on
my mom, and I hated it.
So one day,
I threw a pair
of panties at him
and told him I found them
in the back seat of his car,
and unless
he paid me ten bucks,
I was gonna tell Mom.
The fucker paid me...
...not once,
but for the next three years
every Sunday after church.
But here's the kicker...
I didn't, uh,
find the panties
in his car.
I took 'em from
my mom's drawer.
He didn't even recognize
his own wife's panties.
Fucking idiot...
I mean, you'd think he
would've been pissed,
but it was like
he was grateful,
you know, like I was helping
the bastard make penance.
That's fucked up.
So what made him stop paying
after the three years passed?
Ah, my fucking mom died.
Yeah, she was
fucking great.
Want another?
Yeah.
Can I ask you
a question?
Why are you and Bev
so touch and go?
I could never
figure that out.
I used to gamble...
A lot.
And I hit
a pretty cold streak,
so I forged Bev's signature
and sold my parent's place.
She was fucking pissed,
and, uh...
...then two guys threatened
to kill us both,
so I had
to do something.
Oh.
And that was when you
got into, uh, gay porn.
What? Wait, wait,
Bev told you
I did gay porn?
No. I didn't do
fucking gay porn.
I sucked my own dick.
You... You...
You can suck
your own dick?
You know, I could
when I was 20, but fuck.
I mean, now I got
a bad back.
I eat so many
fucking waffles,
I can't even get to it,
you know?
Strikes me
as a little gay.
I mean, isn't it
just like fucking
masturbating?
Yeah, but you have
a dick in your mouth.
That's pretty impressive,
though, still.
Oh, not again.
You know how to play,
uh, table football?
Yeah.
We're gonna turn
'em up, two posts.
There you go, this is
gonna be real football.
Keep your posts up...
Keep it up like
that, you ready?
Hold it up.
Ready, and oop...
Oh!
I missed, I missed,
here we go.
Okay, ready?
Your turn.
Let's see
if we can get it.
Go ahead.
No, no, you get...
You're the kicker.
Ready to kick it, ready?
One, two, three, go.
Oh!
You almost...
Oh, sh...
Jesus, Tell.
Okay, I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm just gonna
go to the bathroom
really quick.
Can you watch
him, please?
Yeah.
I'll be right
back, okay?
Okay.
You guys
have fun playing.
That... It wasn't me,
it was him.
It was him.
It was me.
Yeah, it was.
Good job.
Yeah.
Here, buddy,
you can have that.
It's your football now.
Hey.
William, do you
think, um...
Do you think
maybe sometime,
you'd want me
to come over
and play football?
Yes.
Yeah?
Okay, okay.
So then maybe when...
When your mom
comes out of the bathroom,
you could tell her.
Say, "I want Tell
to come over
and play football."
She's not my mom.
Buddy... Who is that?
That's Aunt Bev-Bev.
Who?
Oh, evil.
Fuck.
Good as new?
Good as new.
Are you?
Well, almost.
Yeah.
Hey, William...
Good seeing you, bud.
Okay.
He's a great kid.
He looks just like us,
only smaller
and more round.
So, um, when are you
gonna do the job?
Tonight's the job.
Great.
Then, I will
wait for you.
Okay.
Not in front of him.
Right.
Yeah.
Not yet.
Are you ready, bud?
Yeah.
Say bye to Tell...
Bye, Tell.
Bye.
Oh, jeez...
Shit, fucking,
shit, fuck.
What's wrong?
What?
Why are
you so quiet?
No reason.
You nervous?
Hell, no.
I'm just thinking,
what if, uh...
...this Huffman fucker
shows up traveling light?
I don't know...
How light?
Let's say half.
Half, I think
that buys him
about a day.
We're not blackmailing
this guy in installments.
What if he shows up
with 50 or 60 grand?
That's just
an insult.
Anything less
than 100,000,
we're gonna have to
do something
so this guy knows
we mean business.
Did you bring
the bleach?
'Cause I didn't.
There's nothing
to worry about,
this guy's scared.
He wouldn't dare
try and stiff us.
Yeah, he wouldn't
'cause we're no
dumb-ass custodians.
Oh, shit,
there he is.
With a bag.
We're on.
Uh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh-buh.
I, uh, came alone
like you said.
Smart man.
Let's see the green.
Oh.
And my DVDs?
Right here, Fellini.
Toss us the bag,
then you can take
your dirty movies and go.
-  When I was a kid, I thought
-  I was gonna be somebody,
a model citizen raising
a family in the suburbs.
That never happened.
But there is a point
when you find yourself
in a moment, and realize
the decisions
you made were wrong,
and they led you
to a different kind of life.
I should've settled down.
Got a nine-to-five.
Bought a house
with a porch.
Taken my kid
to Pee-Wee football
on the weekends,
and enjoyed the happiness
of not being shot at.
Fuck.
I should've been a doctor...
An accountant...
A goddamn coal miner.
Should've been
anything but this.
Oh, shit, Ray.
Fuck. Just keep
pressure on it.
It's... It's just a little
flesh wound, right?
Yeah, just a scratch.
Come on...
Let's go, we gotta go.
Let's get the fuck
out of here.
We gotta go.
Ah.
Okay, keep that on.
Come on.
Okay.
Hey, guys?
Has the shooting stopped?
Is it safe to come out now?
We would've come out
sooner, but...
Oh, fuck.
I don't know, I was scared.
It sounded dangerous.
Oh, come on,
what the fuck, guys?
Put that pea shooter
on the ground.
On your knees now.
Shit.
Oh, ho-ho, talk about
your textbook crime scene.
I mean, we got the murder
victim, we got the murderer.
This guy tried
to kill us, all right?
I shot in self-defense.
We say different.
You got about two minutes
until our backup shows up
unless you tell us
where the money is.
This entire messy
crime scene goes
away, okay?
You get to go free.
I shot in self-defense.
Ray saw the whole thing.
Fuck you, he'll testify.
That's right, baby.
I'll swear to tell
the whole truth
and nothing
but the goddamn truth.
Fuck.
Fuck, he's right.
He is.
They sure as hell
got us now.
Oh!
What the fuck?
Fuck!
Ray?
You saw that,
he was coming at me.
Oh, yeah.
I was scared.
Son of a bitch... Oh!
In case you haven't
realized it,
we're done screwing around
with you, smart guy.
I warned you
not to piss me off.
I got the money!
Look at this!
It's the fucking money!
What do you mean
you got the money?
Look.
What fucking
money is that?
It's money.
Well, then we don't
need this guy no more.
No, no, no,
that's not the bank money!
That's not the bank money!
What do you mean
it's not the bank money?
There's more,
there's so much more.
There's so much more money.
That's not
the bank money, please.
Where's it at?
Where is it?
Jefferson.
I told you!
I told you
it was at the Jefferson.
Come on, come on, come on.
All right, smart guy,
get up. Let's go.
¶
This is exactly
a half a million dollars.
No shit!
Son of a bitch.
Are there any marks?
No, looks
like it's clean.
50-50, right?
70-30.
No, no.
50-50, that's the bank money.
This is other money.
No, kiddo,
70-30, that's our split.
In six months, I'm headed
to retirement.
Trust me,
20 years from now,
you won't remember
any of this stuff.
You tell her the same thing
the second time.
Which way?
Service stairs,
down two floors.
Come on, let's go.
Where?
It's jammed
inside the panel
in back of
the third machine!
You climbed back there
with a bullet in your gut?
You're going!
You're going
with him!
You gotta help me
pull it off!
Well?
He's looking for it!
What?
He's got the bag!
¶
It's okay.
I'm a cop!
It's all right,
I do this for a living!
go backwards.
Stay in your car.
Don't get out of your...
I told you
I was a bad-ass.
Whoa!
Half of the bank money.
There's 500,000 in there.
Are you
fucking kidding me?
I knew you
fucking had it.
I knew you had it
all along.
Okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, but there is
an "I" in let's get
the fuck out of here.
Let's go, come on.
Let's go!
First thing I'm gonna do
is buy me a car
I can fit my fat ass in!
Jesus, Tell.
What happened?
Ray didn't come
home last night.
The whole thing
went wrong.
We thought the guy
was gonna roll over and...
...but he had a gun.
He shot Ray?
They all shot Ray.
And the money?
Wow.
Took you less than 30 seconds
to ask about the money.
The whole point
of this was the
money, wasn't it?
Meaning what? That...
That as long
as I got the money,
it doesn't matter
that Ray's dead?
Don't you make
me the bad guy.
Don't you
do that to me!
You guys were the
idiots who were
blackmailing him, not me!
That's all you ever have been,
is about the money.
Where is this coming from?
You lied to me
about William,
and you don't care
if I get hurt,
or if that
little boy gets hurt,
as long as you get...
Your money.
I didn't lie
about William.
He's not my kid!
Fuck, he's not even
your kid, Aunt Beverly.
Who said that?
William.
He is my son.
He is our son.
So you're telling me
he doesn't know
who his mother is?
That's... That's
what you're saying?
That's exactly
what I'm saying.
When I gave birth...
...my cousin Margaret
was with me,
and I didn't have
a job or a place to go,
so she and her
fiance offered to...
...take him.
And I let them.
They are his parents
as far as anyone knows.
She's his mom.
God, she's his mom...
...and I'm just
Aunt Beverly.
Aunt Beverly who lives
in the bungalow out back.
Aunt Beverly who baby-sits
all the time,
who can't stop
kissing and hugging him.
That's why
I needed the money...
...so I could get
my son back.
So we could
be a family.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, Bev?
Yeah?
You think you could loan me
a couple bucks?
What for?
If it's there,
we'll find it.
Fucking morons.
You look beautiful.
What are you
doing here?
Aren't you supposed
to be holed up?
Yeah, I'm gonna get out
of town for a while
till this thing
blows over,
but, um, before I go,
I have something for you.
What's this?
Um, you said
if I had the money,
I could be a part
of William's life.
That's the money.
I figured William
should have Ray's
end of the deal...
Considering
what happened.
Are you serious?
This is mine?
This changes everything.
We can be together now,
You, me, William...
No, no, Bev, Bev.
It's William's.
It's not yours.
Come on, look at him.
Look at him.
It's one better than our
fucked-up shit can give him.
You and me, we're broken.
We can't change that,
money can't change that.
This gives
him a chance.
He's a lucky kid.
He's got doting parents
and an aunt who would
literally kill for him.
I'm gonna go.
65, 70.
One, two, three, four. Huh?
Thank you, father.
Hey, you did
a fantastic job this week.
You earned it.
To me, it never
really was about
the money.
Thank you.
Life doesn't always work out
the way you thought it would.
The decisions you make
stick to you,
make you the person you are,
and make your life what it is.
But you know what
the funny thing about life is?
Sometimes, sometimes...
...it gives you
a second chance.
¶
¶ Your eyes
¶ They're gonna
watch every move
¶ They're gonna watch
until everyone
¶ Has turned around
¶ Everyone has turned around,
and I
¶ I wanna
put my trust in you
¶ And try to put some faith
in anything
¶ We can work it out
¶ But everything's
gonna work around you
¶ Till I realized
I was under a spell
¶ Oh
¶ And you only care
about yourself
¶ Whoa, oh, oh
¶ Wasted time
waiting for you
¶ So I'm gonna find
somebody new
¶ Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa
¶ It's you
¶ Wasted time
waiting for you
¶ I'm gonna find
somebody new
¶ Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa
¶ It's you
¶
¶ Whoa, whoa
¶ Whoa
¶ Lies, try them
on someone else
¶ I'm tired of giving
everything I have to you
¶ Everything I have
¶ And I, I'm through
with all your pettiness
¶ I'm gonna make an act of
wisdom, grace, and elegance
¶ You'll never see
my face around here
¶ And I realized
I was under your spell
¶ Oh, oh
¶ 'Cause you only care
about yourself
¶ Whoa, oh, oh
¶ Wasted time
waiting for you
¶ So I'm gonna find
somebody new
¶ Whoa, whoa,
whoa, oh, whoa, oh
¶ It's you
¶ Wasted time
waiting for you
¶ And I'm gonna find
somebody new
¶ Somebody new
¶ Whoa
¶ Where's the love
that was lost?
¶ And all your memories
¶ Now gone
¶ Wasted time
waiting for you
¶ I'm gonna find
somebody new
¶ Whoa, whoa,
whoa, oh, whoa, oh
¶ It's you
¶ Wasted time
waiting for you
¶ I'm gonna find
somebody new
¶ Somebody new
¶
¶ Whoa, whoa
¶ Whoa, whoa ¶